const level9questions = [
    {
        "question": "3 less than 150?",
        "options": ["481", "250", "599", "147"],
        "answer": "147"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 more than 558?",
        "options": ["905", "823", "564", "415"],
        "answer": "564"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 195?",
        "options": ["188", "123", "642", "99"],
        "answer": "188"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 116?",
        "options": ["38", "948", "374", "108"],
        "answer": "108"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 more than 981?",
        "options": ["860", "309", "343", "984"],
        "answer": "984"
      },
      {
        "question": "2 less than 512?",
        "options": ["715", "765", "510", "919"],
        "answer": "510"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 more than 682?",
        "options": ["801", "1001", "543", "686"],
        "answer": "686"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 123?",
        "options": ["72", "490", "645", "115"],
        "answer": "115"
      },
      {
        "question": "1 more than 18?",
        "options": ["19", "48", "25", "731"],
        "answer": "19"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 383?",
        "options": ["582", "795", "278", "377"],
        "answer": "377"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 more than 60?",
        "options": ["810", "187", "64", "707"],
        "answer": "64"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 more than 441?",
        "options": ["456", "569", "193", "448"],
        "answer": "448"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 more than 962?",
        "options": ["965", "232", "25", "927"],
        "answer": "965"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 855?",
        "options": ["847", "963", "764", "926"],
        "answer": "847"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 more than 936?",
        "options": ["944", "898", "67", "462"],
        "answer": "944"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 more than 193?",
        "options": ["558", "477", "462", "198"],
        "answer": "198"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 more than 248?",
        "options": ["731", "820", "254", "734"],
        "answer": "254"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 more than 113?",
        "options": ["241", "119", "619", "411"],
        "answer": "119"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 more than 488?",
        "options": ["736", "867", "491", "447"],
        "answer": "491"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 692?",
        "options": ["464", "488", "682", "660"],
        "answer": "682"
      },
      {
        "question": "1 less than 370?",
        "options": ["576", "162", "369", "610"],
        "answer": "369"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 808?",
        "options": ["798", "32", "980", "23"],
        "answer": "798"
      },
      {
        "question": "1 less than 889?",
        "options": ["888", "264", "716", "141"],
        "answer": "888"
      },
      {
        "question": "1 less than 37?",
        "options": ["746", "157", "866", "36"],
        "answer": "36"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 more than 357?",
        "options": ["610", "366", "499", "373"],
        "answer": "366"
      },
    
      {
        "question": "3 less than 895?",
        "options": ["237", "792", "892", "791"],
        "answer": "792"
      },
      {
        "question": "2 more than 756?",
        "options": ["824", "758", "377", "28"],
        "answer": "758"
      },
      {
        "question": "1 less than 413?",
        "options": ["576", "153", "657", "412"],
        "answer": "412"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 more than 412?",
        "options": ["539", "293", "417", "862"],
        "answer": "417"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 more than 561?",
        "options": ["176", "429", "679", "565"],
        "answer": "565"
      },
      {
        "question": "2 less than 651?",
        "options": ["123", "649", "660", "575"],
        "answer": "649"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 more than 490?",
        "options": ["824", "643", "574", "497"],
        "answer": "497"
      },
      {
        "question": "2 less than 884?",
        "options": ["481", "882", "787", "111"],
        "answer": "882"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 781?",
        "options": ["818", "547", "854", "774"],
        "answer": "774"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 640?",
        "options": ["544", "908", "703", "633"],
        "answer": "633"
      },
      {
        "question": "2 more than 755?",
        "options": ["757", "536", "142", "990"],
        "answer": "757"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 more than 755?",
        "options": ["763", "96", "13", "509"],
        "answer": "763"
      },
      {
        "question": "1 less than 764?",
        "options": ["763", "921", "698", "862"],
        "answer": "763"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 213?",
        "options": ["224", "261", "203", "621"],
        "answer": "203"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 50?",
        "options": ["64", "241", "41", "844"],
        "answer": "41"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 605?",
        "options": ["599", "120", "624", "399"],
        "answer": "599"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 46?",
        "options": ["39", "816", "16", "533"],
        "answer": "39"
      },
      {
        "question": "2 less than 538?",
        "options": ["851", "174", "536", "95"],
        "answer": "536"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 540?",
        "options": ["536", "288", "232", "905"],
        "answer": "536"
      },
      {
        "question": "1 less than 731?",
        "options": ["448", "113", "327", "730"],
        "answer": "730"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 more than 207?",
        "options": ["88", "393", "829", "212"],
        "answer": "212"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 more than 316?",
        "options": ["876", "214", "320", "862"],
        "answer": "320"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 654?",
        "options": ["8", "108", "644", "830"],
        "answer": "644"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 783?",
        "options": ["553", "620", "774", "289"],
        "answer": "774"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 977?",
        "options": ["971", "200", "265", "868"],
        "answer": "971"
      },
    
      {
        "question": "4 more than 28?",
        "options": ["671", "445", "63", "32"],
        "answer": "32"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 815?",
        "options": ["707", "806", "454", "566"],
        "answer": "806"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 311?",
        "options": ["793", "13", "510", "304"],
        "answer": "304"
      },
      {
        "question": "2 more than 724?",
        "options": ["298", "726", "850", "710"],
        "answer": "726"
      },
      {
        "question": "2 less than 555?",
        "options": ["832", "113", "589", "553"],
        "answer": "553"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 more than 266?",
        "options": ["810", "273", "723", "141"],
        "answer": "273"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 more than 251?",
        "options": ["528", "411", "261", "716"],
        "answer": "261"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 733?",
        "options": ["723", "231", "558", "14"],
        "answer": "723"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 931?",
        "options": ["658", "928", "251", "236"],
        "answer": "928"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 646?",
        "options": ["298", "692", "988", "640"],
        "answer": "640"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 994?",
        "options": ["19", "729", "986", "963"],
        "answer": "986"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 470?",
        "options": ["64", "520", "464", "702"],
        "answer": "464"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 more than 462?",
        "options": ["472", "1008", "509", "598"],
        "answer": "472"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 more than 14?",
        "options": ["753", "194", "24", "132"],
        "answer": "24"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 107?",
        "options": ["827", "324", "797", "104"],
        "answer": "104"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 more than 799?",
        "options": ["803", "216", "701", "479"],
        "answer": "803"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 more than 488?",
        "options": ["961", "491", "394", "293"],
        "answer": "491"
      },
      {
        "question": "1 less than 658?",
        "options": ["297", "11", "657", "124"],
        "answer": "657"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 261?",
        "options": ["610", "740", "253", "862"],
        "answer": "253"
      },
      {
        "question": "1 less than 504?",
        "options": ["503", "674", "205", "159"],
        "answer": "503"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 396?",
        "options": ["389", "57", "955", "861"],
        "answer": "389"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 more than 11?",
        "options": ["667", "637", "607", "19"],
        "answer": "19"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 more than 244?",
        "options": ["401", "742", "815", "251"],
        "answer": "251"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 412?",
        "options": ["405", "317", "726", "631"],
        "answer": "405"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 553?",
        "options": ["989", "741", "550", "429"],
        "answer": "550"
      },
    
      {
        "question": "2 more than 172?",
        "options": ["174", "872", "147", "759"],
        "answer": "174"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 more than 622?",
        "options": ["889", "626", "90", "410"],
        "answer": "626"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 more than 400?",
        "options": ["474", "693", "766", "404"],
        "answer": "404"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 910?",
        "options": ["528", "662", "102", "906"],
        "answer": "906"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 more than 19?",
        "options": ["432", "28", "689", "359"],
        "answer": "28"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 more than 758?",
        "options": ["780", "942", "768", "151"],
        "answer": "768"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 more than 987?",
        "options": ["680", "993", "73", "315"],
        "answer": "993"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 more than 503?",
        "options": ["489", "508", "131", "87"],
        "answer": "508"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 more than 58?",
        "options": ["62", "152", "118", "103"],
        "answer": "62"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 more than 940?",
        "options": ["536", "897", "205", "948"],
        "answer": "948"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 more than 190?",
        "options": ["196", "704", "925", "870"],
        "answer": "196"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 more than 448?",
        "options": ["328", "115", "396", "455"],
        "answer": "455"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 372?",
        "options": ["592", "365", "279", "503"],
        "answer": "365"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 954?",
        "options": ["760", "907", "979", "945"],
        "answer": "945"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 488?",
        "options": ["483", "937", "844", "167"],
        "answer": "483"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 more than 602?",
        "options": ["17", "763", "605", "543"],
        "answer": "605"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 more than 283?",
        "options": ["643", "263", "855", "287"],
        "answer": "287"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 99?",
        "options": ["872", "338", "621", "92"],
        "answer": "92"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 more than 990?",
        "options": ["994", "1000", "992", "998"],
        "answer": "994"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 668?",
        "options": ["346", "663", "683", "647"],
        "answer": "663"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 172?",
        "options": ["370", "168", "11", "831"],
        "answer": "168"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 165?",
        "options": ["360", "57", "457", "162"],
        "answer": "162"
      },
      {
        "question": "2 more than 381?",
        "options": ["177", "362", "395", "383"],
        "answer": "383"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 803?",
        "options": ["797", "248", "409", "573"],
        "answer": "797"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 726?",
        "options": ["449", "720", "42", "788"],
        "answer": "720"
      },
];
export default level9questions;